Listen to part of a radio program about nature.
The camel is an example of an animal that is especially adapted to survive in harsh conditions.
First of all，camels have humps on their backs.
Now many people think that camels hold water in their humps.But that is actually not true.
While camels do have to store water, what they carry in their humps is not water but fat.
That’s their emergency supply of energy in case there’s little food to eat.
Of course camels wouldn’t need to carry a safety supply of fat if it
were easy to find something to eat where they live.
Unfortunately in a desert, camels can sometimes walk for days in the hot sun looking for food and water.
So when there is little to eat，the fat from their hump allows them to
survive for quite a long time, even up to two weeks without eating anything.
When they do get an opportunity to eat and drink, camels consume as much as possible.
A camel can drink incredible amounts of water，a lot more than most other animals
can take in without getting sick.
You see, there’s a limit on how much an animal can drink.
If an animal were to drink more than necessary,
that could even be bad for that animal’s health.
But a camel’s body does not suffer the effects of too much water.
After it has stored up plenty of food and water, it can go on
for days in a hot desert.